<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<ImageGallery ImageDir="static/img/galleries/2004_summer_camp_at_rotary_scout_reservation" ThumbnailOutputDir="static/img/galleries/2004_summer_camp_at_rotary_scout_reservation/thumbnails/" DefaultThumbnailScale="0.70">
  <Image FileName="rsr2004_0_2.jpg">
    <Alt>A patch with a light blue background and a dark blue phoenix with a thunder bold in the center of its chest.  It says "Twin Rivers Council Rotary Scout Reservation 2004."</Alt>
    <Caption>The patch scouts and adults earned by camping at Rotary in 2004.</Caption>
    <ThumbnailScale>0.99</ThumbnailScale>
  </Image>
  <Image FileName="rsr_2004_15_1.jpg">
    <Alt>5 scouts sit around a picnic table.  Four are facing to the right, one is facing to the left.</Alt>
    <Caption>First year scouts sit at a picnic table.</Caption>
    <ThumbnailScale>0.818317751174515</ThumbnailScale>
  </Image>
  <Image FileName="rsr2004_1_3.jpg">
    <Alt>A scout is looking at a bulletin board that is hanging on a tree.</Alt>
    <ThumbnailScale>0.8767064646667335</ThumbnailScale>
  </Image>
  <Image FileName="rsr2004_2_4.jpg">
    <Alt>A scout is holding an ave over his head, looking at a log on the ground that is standing up vertically.</Alt>
    <Caption>Chopping wood!</Caption>
    <ThumbnailScale>0.99</ThumbnailScale>
  </Image>
  <Image FileName="rsr2004_3_5.jpg">
    <Alt>A scout wearing a red Troop 53 class B tee-shirt and wearing a baithing suit looking at the camera.</Alt>
    <ThumbnailScale>0.99</ThumbnailScale>
  </Image>
  <Image FileName="rsr2004_9_11.jpg">
    <Alt>A man sitting in a camping chair in the sunlight.  Behind are two cabin tents.</Alt>
    <Caption>Scoutmaster, Don McKnight, soaking up the sun.</Caption>
    <ThumbnailScale>0.795919358756376</ThumbnailScale>
  </Image>
  <Image FileName="rsr2004_5_7.jpg">
    <Alt>Four people are staring at a fire pit.  Two of them are holding chickens over the fire pit.</Alt>
    <Caption>Scouts and adults trying to cook dinner, which is BBQ chicken.</Caption>
    <ThumbnailScale>0.8227067876824966</ThumbnailScale>
  </Image>
  <Image FileName="rsr2004_7_9.jpg">
    <Alt>Two people walking towards the camera talking to each other. The person on the right is wet, and wrapped in a towel.</Alt>
    <ThumbnailScale>0.9093807292904309</ThumbnailScale>
  </Image>
  <Image FileName="rsr2004_8_10.jpg">
    <Alt>Three people smiling at the camera.  The two at the ends are wearing class A uniforms.</Alt>
    <ThumbnailScale>0.99</ThumbnailScale>
  </Image>
  <Image FileName="rsr2004_10_12.jpg">
    <Alt>Scoutmaster McKnight talking to Seth Hendrick, who is wearing a colorful felt parrot hat.</Alt>
    <Caption>Scout, Seth Hendrick, wearing a parrot hat to go with the camp's pirate theme for the year.</Caption>
    <ThumbnailScale>0.9740929561973275</ThumbnailScale>
  </Image>
  <Image FileName="rsr2004_13_15.jpg">
    <Alt>Two scouts in class A uniforms talking to each other, smiling.  Surrounding htem are 5 other people.</Alt>
    <Caption>Scouts visiting their families.</Caption>
    <ThumbnailScale>0.9976195867480815</ThumbnailScale>
  </Image>
  <Image FileName="rsr2004_6_8.jpg">
    <Alt>Two people standing on the camera.  The scout on the right is holding the Michael Dikant Award.</Alt>
    <Caption>Dustin Albertine (right) receiving the Michael Dikant Annual Honor Scout Award. To the left is Bill Dikant.</Caption>
    <ThumbnailScale>0.99</ThumbnailScale>
  </Image>
  <Image FileName="rsr2004_11_13.jpg">
    <Alt>Two adults stand on either side of a scout, who is bent over sawing a log with a bow saw.</Alt>
    <Caption>Adult leaders supervise cutting wood for the fire.</Caption>
    <ThumbnailScale>0.7407803026770714</ThumbnailScale>
  </Image>
  <Image FileName="rsr2004_4_6.jpg">
    <Alt>Three scouts smile for the camera.</Alt>
    <Caption>Scouts prepare to leave the campsite overnight to fulfil a Camping merit badge requirement.</Caption>
    <ThumbnailScale>0.9587138348333961</ThumbnailScale>
  </Image>
  <Image FileName="rsr2004_12_14.jpg">
    <Alt>There are three scouts holding a stretched out bow, ready to shoot.</Alt>
    <Caption>Scouts shooting archery.</Caption>
    <ThumbnailScale>0.99</ThumbnailScale>
  </Image>
  <Image FileName="rsr2004_16_18.jpg">
    <Alt>Two scouts at the archery range.  Both are smiling, and facing right.</Alt>
    <ThumbnailScale>0.99</ThumbnailScale>
  </Image>
  <Image FileName="rsr2004_14_16.jpg">
    <Alt>Two scouts are sitting at a picnic table.  The one on the right is looking at a compass.</Alt>
    <ThumbnailScale>0.8482265785901612</ThumbnailScale>
  </Image>
  <Image FileName="rsr2004_15_17.jpg">
    <Alt>Two scouts weaving baskets.  The one in the middle is wearing a blue hat, the one on the right is wearing the red troop hat.  There's a scout on the left writing something on a clipboard.</Alt>
    <Caption>Scouts weave stools for the Basketry merit badge.</Caption>
    <ThumbnailScale>0.99</ThumbnailScale>
  </Image>
  <Image FileName="rsr_20_20.jpg">
    <Alt>Three scouts are running towards something, while two scouts off to the right watch.</Alt>
    <Caption>First year scouts playing in a field.</Caption>
    <ThumbnailScale>0.99</ThumbnailScale>
  </Image>
  <Image FileName="rsr2004_21_21.jpg">
    <Alt>Three canoes are in thie picture, each of which have two people with life jackets on.</Alt>
    <ThumbnailScale>0.9891125327557876</ThumbnailScale>
  </Image>
  <Image FileName="rsr2004_22_22.jpg">
    <Alt>Two people in a canoe that has been swamped.  The canoe is just under the water surface.</Alt>
    <Caption>Scoutmaster McKnight taking on water.</Caption>
    <ThumbnailScale>0.7876094761668695</ThumbnailScale>
  </Image>
  <Image FileName="rsr2004_17_19.jpg">
    <Alt>27 people in class A uniforms smiling for the camera in front of an American flag pole.  To the left is a scout holding the US flag, to the right is another scout holding the Troop flag.</Alt>
    <Caption>Troop photo at Rotary Scout Reservation in 2004.</Caption>
    <ThumbnailScale>0.99</ThumbnailScale>
  </Image>
</ImageGallery>