<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<ImageGallery ImageDir="static/img/galleries/2007_washington_dc_trip" ThumbnailOutputDir="static/img/galleries/2007_washington_dc_trip/thumbnails/" DefaultThumbnailScale="0.70">
    <Image FileName="dctrip_may_12_2007_0001.jpg">
        <Alt>A crowd of people walking towards the Vietnam Veterans Memorial Wall.</Alt>
        <Caption>Scouts visiting the Vietnam Veterans Memorial Wall.</Caption>
    </Image>
    <Image FileName="dctrip_may_12_2007_0002.jpg">
        <Alt>A man in a white Troop 53 class B tee-shirt facing the camera smiling.  In the background, scouts sit looking at waterfalls.</Alt>
        <Caption>Assistant Scoutmaster, Kevin Shaw, smiling for the camera while scouts take a break at the FDR Memorial.</Caption>
    </Image>
    <Image FileName="dctrip_may_12_2007_0003.jpg">
        <Alt>Photo of the Lincoln Memorial from the outside.  Scouts are halfway up walking towards the enterance.</Alt>
        <Caption>Scouts visiting the Lincoln Memorial.</Caption>
    </Image>
    <Image FileName="dctrip_may_12_2007_0007.jpg">
        <Alt>Photo of the Jefferson Memorial.  A group of scouts are walking up the stairs.</Alt>
        <Caption>Scouts walking up the stairs of the Jefferson Memorial.</Caption>
    </Image>
    <Image FileName="dctrip_may_12_2007_0006.jpg">
        <Alt>Two scouts taking a drink from water fountains.</Alt>
        <Caption>Taking a water break.</Caption>
    </Image>
    <Image FileName="dctrip_may_12_2007_0004.jpg">
        <Alt>Photo of the US capital, with two scouts in class A uniforms walking towards the stairs.</Alt>
    </Image>
  <Image FileName="img_3108.jpg_2.jpg">
    <Alt>Four scouts standing with the Washington Monument in the background.  The three to the right are wearing Class A uniforms, the scout on the left is wearing a red Class B.</Alt>
    <Caption>Scouts in front of the reflecting pool.</Caption>
    <ThumbnailScale>0.99</ThumbnailScale>
  </Image>
  <Image FileName="img_3109.jpg_3.jpg">
    <Alt>Five scouts sitting in front of a water fall fountain.</Alt>
    <Caption>Scouts take a break at the FDR Memorial.</Caption>
    <ThumbnailScale>0.99</ThumbnailScale>
  </Image>
</ImageGallery>
